a useful tool within word is the final
éclairs tool this allows you to search
through a document for a specific word
and then replace it with another word
this could be very useful if you have a
large document and you need to find
instances of a word that may appear 100
200 times and it needs to be changed
quickly as an example I have a letter on
the screen and where I'm going to use
the final replace tool to change the
word data to information there are
several instances of the word theatre
and so I click on the editing tool
select replace and the word I'm looking
for is deer and going to replace that
with information there are three options
here so you can replace and that will
replace each instance one at a time so
you can just confirm that this is okay
or you can select the place order this
will automatically the whole document
and replace every instance of the word
theatre with information it's good to be
careful with this because there may be
certain words are a part of other words
an example of this is Nate aim name
Mayer so if you are looking to change
the word Nate into something else and
those words were present in that
document it would automatically change
the first part of that word into
whatever he had decided to change it
into so for this one here I'm just going
to change deer I with information and
I'll go through one of the temps for
select replace as you can see it's
highlighted the word deer died so I
click replace the second instances
appeared click the place and replace the
place where there's no finish search in
the document and I can close up and
every instance of the word theater has
been replaced with the word information